Robert <u>Adam **Hinke**l</u>

7704 Baederwood Terrace, Rockville, MD 20855 || C: (240)-351-3522 || AHinkel421@gmail.com

Summary

Reliable and driven Web Developer who quickly learns and masters new concepts. Hands on experience with the design, development, testing, debugging, and continuous integration of web applications. Productive and efficient with the ability to multi-task. Self-directed team player who also works well independently. Transitioning from a financial background to a career in Web Development. Currently a student and Junior Mentor at Thinkful (Web Development Bootcamp).

Highlights

- Experience with HTML5, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, NodeJS, React
- Excellent attention to detail, design, and UX awareness
- Well versed in industry best practices
- Works well on a team, or individually
- Strong written and oral communication skills

Experience

<u>Thinkful</u> (Independent Contractor) (Washington, D.C.)

June 2017 - Present

Junior Mentor -

Responsible for providing services to students by answering their questions, helping them understand new concepts, sharing industry best practices, and motivating them to reach their goals. Oversees Thinkful's public workshops and assists students, and visitors alike, in learning new concepts. Ensures that anyone having trouble is attended to and helped in a friendly, encouraging manner.

<u>BSI Financial Services</u> (Bethesda, MD)

April 2016 - March 2017

Foreclosure Analyst -

Was selected and hired as a full time employee from a contract-to-hire position (Same job description as Greylocke and Company, below).

*Greylocke and Company's contract with BSI was terminated in April 2016. 3 of Greylocke and Company's 10 employees were hired, full time.

Greylocke & Company (contractor on behalf of BSI Financial Services)

(Bethesda, MD)

August 2015 - April 2016

Foreclosure Analyst -

Responsible for servicing default loans from the date of default through the foreclosure sale. Aggressively followed up with, and managed attorneys to ensure the foreclosure process was being expedited on a daily basis. Maintained current foreclosure status on a weekly basis for 500-800 files, in all systems of records used by BSI. Responded and followed up to all requests from internal and external contacts in a timely and professional manner.

Harris Teeter (Darnestown, MD)

January 2015 - August 2015

Cashier/Customer Service Representative -

Responsible for processing transactions in a timely and professional manner while delivering the utmost level of customer service. Maintains security and control over all funds within the cash register. Assists customers in selecting products to best fit their needs.

Education

Thinkful Web Development Bootcamp $\parallel April$ 2017 Present Web Development

Online/Washington, D.C.

Montgomery College || 2011-2013 General Studies Rockville, MD

Col. Zadok Magruder High School || 2011 High School Diploma Rockville, MD

Portfolio

bit.ly/goalstrive

https://ahinkel421.github.io/zipadopt/

https://ahinkel421.github.io/Trial-By-Trivia-App/